<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AnimeNews </string>
    <string name="nav_open">Open</string>
    <string name="nav_close">Close</string>

    <string name="news_1"> This year\'s 52nd issue of Shueisha\'s Weekly Shonen Jump magazine revealed on Monday that the television anime of Kenichi Kondō\'s Dark Gathering manga will debut in summer 2023. The anime stars Yū Sasahara as Yayoi Hо̄zuki, Nobunaga Shimazaki as Keitarо̄ Gentо̄ga, and Kana Hanazawa as Eiko Hо̄zuki. Hiroshi Ikehata (FLCL Progressive, Kiratto Pri☆Chan, Space Battleship Tiramisu) is directing the anime at OLM. Shigeru Murakoshi (I\'m Quitting Heroing, Zombie Land Saga) is overseeing the series scripts, and Shin\'ya Segawa (Pastel Memories, Garakowa -Restore the World-) is the character designer. Kohta Yamamoto, Shun Narita, and Yūsuke Seo are composing the music. Other staff members include Taijirō Nagata as art director, Yuho Ando as director of photography, Takahiro Uezono as 3D director, Ritsuko Utagawa as color designer, and Kōhei Yoshida as sound director. Kondō (Cheer Danshi!! GO BREAKERS manga) launched the manga in Shueisha\'s Jump SQ. magazine in March 2019. </string>
    <string name="news_2">That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime Film Earns 416 Million Yen in 1st 3 Days. The anime film That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime: Scarlet Bond (Tensei Shitara Slime Datta Ken: Guren no Kizuna-hen) sold 313,000 tickets and earned 416 million yen (about US$3.19 million) in its first three days. The film opened in Japan last Friday. The movie sold 225,000 tickets and earned 297 million yen (about US$2.15 million) on Saturday and Sunday, ranking second on the box office chart in its first weekend screening. Crunchyroll will screen the film in all major global territories (excluding Asia) in early 2023. The film\'s rollout overseas will start in December, and will eventually include the United States, the United Kingdom, Australia, New Zealand, South Africa, Canada, France, Germany, South Korea, Taiwan, Hong Kong, and South and Central America. The staff is planning to screen the film in other countries and regions.</string>
    <string name="news_3">Suzume Anime Film Earns 6.26 Billion Yen in 17 Days. Film has sold a cumulative total of 4.60 million tickets. The Mainichi Shimbun\'s Mantan Web reported on Monday that Makoto Shinkai\'s Suzume (Suzume no Tojimari) anime film has crossed 6.269 billion yen (about US$45.5 million) in its first 17 days at the Japanese box office. The film has sold a cumulative total of 4.60 million tickets. The film earned 843 million yen (US$6.10 million) on Saturday and Sunday and sold 612,000 tickets on the same two days, ranking at #1 for the weekend. The film opened at #1 on November 11 and sold 1.33 million tickets and earned 1.88 billion yen (about US$13.49 million) in its first three days. The film sold 38.7% more tickets and earned 47.4% more than Shinkai\'s acclaimed your name. film, which earned 1,277,960,000 yen (about US$12.51 million at the time) in its first three days. It also sold 14.8% more tickets and earned 14.4% more than Shinkai\'s previous film Weathering With You, marking the strongest opening three days of Shinkai\'s films.</string>
    <string name="news_4">Bullbuster Anime Streams \'Ultra Teaser\' Video With Animated Footage. Studio NuT, Hero Mask director Hiroyasu Aoki\'s 2023 series about "economically viable robot heroes." Kadokawa\'s official YouTube channel began streaming an "ultra teaser" video for the upcoming television anime of the Bullbuster franchise on Sunday. The teaser is the first reveal of the anime\'s footage. The franchise had a stage presentation at the Kitakyushu Pop Culture Festival event on Sunday.In the anime\'s story, a young engineer named Tetsurō Okino who has developed the new robot Bullbuster is transferred to Hato Industries, a company that exterminates harmful animals. There, the company and its president Kōji Tajima are up against a mysterious lifeform named "Kyojū." As a small business that is always finding itself short on money, Hato must always account for every expense such as fuel and pilot labor. And of course, missed shots are not tolerated. The company is always stuck between their ideals of Kyōju extermination and the reality of the economy.</string>
    <string name="news_5">\'Don\'t Toy with Me, Miss Nagatoro 2nd Attack\' TV Anime\'s 2nd Promo Video Previews Opening Theme. The official website for the anime of Nanashi\'s Don\'t Toy with Me, Miss Nagatoro (Ijiranaide, Nagatoro-san) manga began streaming a second promotional video on Friday for the second season, Don\'t Toy with Me, Miss Nagatoro 2nd Attack (Ijiranaide, Nagatoro-san 2nd Attack). The video previews Uesaka\'s opening theme song "LOVE CRAZY."</string>
    <string name="news_6">Flaglia Anime Reveals 13 More Cast Members. The official website for the FLAGLIA project\'s anime revealed the anime\'s main cast on Friday. The anime\'s full title is Flaglia: Natsuyasumi no Monogatari (FLAGLIA: Story of Summer Vacation). Cast members include: (character name romanizations not confirmed) Mark Ishii as Tagi, Junya Enoki as Ren, Takeo Ōtsuka as Mel, Seiichirō Yamashita as Kanchi, Yōhei Azakami as Tetsu, Shunichi Toki as Silver, Yoshitaka Yamaya as Rabu, Eiji Takeuchi as Nitta, Katsunori Okai as Mythril, Kensuke Nishi as Hasshu, Takuya Masumoto as Marie, Takugo Iwakawa as Jango, Hiromi Igarashi as Iko, The project aims to "connect anime and musicals," and will also include a stage musical production.</string>
    <string name="news_7">Mob Psycho 100 III Anime Unveils Final Arc\'s Promo Video. The official website for Mob Psycho 100 III, the third season of the television anime of ONE\'s Mob Psycho 100 manga, began streaming a new promotional video for the anime\'s final arc on Thursday.The anime premiered on October 5 on Tokyo MX and BS Fuji and on October 7 on Cartoon Network in Japan. Crunchyroll is streaming the anime worldwide excluding Asia in Japanese with English subtitles and with an English dub as it airs in Japan. The first two episodes screened during the Crunchyroll Expo convention. Setsuo Ito, Takahiro Sakurai, Akio Ohtsuka, Miyu Irino, and Yoshitsugu Matsuoka are all reprising their roles as Shigeo "Mob" Kageyama, Arataka Reigen, Ekubo, Ritsu Kageyama, and Teruki Hanazawa, respectively.</string>
    <string name="news_8">Jujutsu Kaisen 0 Tops Weathering With You as 6th Biggest Anime Film of All Time Globally. The staff for the Jujutsu Kaisen 0 anime film revealed on Thursday that the film sold over 20.51 million tickets to earn over 26.5 billion yen (about US$191.1 million) worldwide. The Numbers website lists the film with a worldwide box office total of US$195,870,885. That puts Jujutsu Kaisen 0 above Weathering With You\'s all-time worldwide earnings of US$189,981,720 — making Jujutsu Kaisen 0 the sixth highest-earning anime film of all time worldwide, unadjusted for inflation. Currently, only Demon Slayer – Kimetsu no Yaiba – The Movie: Mugen Train, three Hayao Miyazaki films (Spirited Away, Howl\'s Moving Castle, Ponyo), and Makoto Shinkai\'s your name. have earned more than Jujutsu Kaisen 0 worldwide. The film screened in 89 countries and regions, selling 10.67 million tickets for over 12.7 billion yen (around US$91.4 million) outside Jaoan. The film is the fourth highest-earning Japanese film in the U.S.</string>
    <string name="news_9">By the Grace of the Gods Season 2 Anime Reveals January 8 Debut. The official website for the anime of author Roy and illustrator Ririnra\'s By the Grace of the Gods (Kami-tachi ni Hirowareta Otoko) light novel series revealed 12 characters, a key visual, and January 8 premiere for the anime\'s second season on Friday. The newly revealed characters include: (character name romanizations not confirmed) Makoto Yasumura as Serge. Junya Enoki as Dorche, Risa Kubota as Carla, Sakura Nakamura as Calum Hiro Shimono as Tony, Kenichi Suzumura as Pioro, Daisuke Hirakawa as Prenance, Tetsu Inada as Worgan</string>
    <string name="news_10">Kaina of the Great Snow Sea Anime\'s Trailer Unveils More Staff, Theme Songs, January 11 Debut. The official website for Kaina of the Great Snow Sea (Ōyukiumi no Kaina), the new television anime project from BLAME! and Knights of Sidonia collaborators Tsutomu Nihei and Polygon Pictures, unveiled the full trailer and a main visual for the anime on Wednesday. The trailer reveals more staff members, reveals and previews yorushika\'s opening theme song "Telepath" and GReeeeN\'s ending theme song "Juvenile," and reveals the anime\'s January 11 premiere date on Fuji TV\'s Ultra+ block. The staff members include: Animation Character Design: Ryōhei Fukushi, Kyoko Kotani, Visual Concept Design: Mitsunori Kataama, Production Design: Naoya Tanaka, Kazuma Teshigahara, CG Supervisors: Takuma Ishibashi, Masaki Taga, Art Director: Kimiko Kubo, 3D BG Matte Paint Supervisor: Yoshikatsu Matsumoto, Color Key Artist: Hironori Nochi, Chief Layout Animation Supervisor: Kazumasa Izawa, Sound Director: Masanori Tsuchiya, Music: Kohta Yamamoto (Attack on Titan The Final Season, Sacrificial Princess And the King of Beasts), Misaki Umase</string>

    <string name="youtube_1">VUL4yEyvjxA</string>
    <string name="youtube_2">M4EPHOfgOdc</string>
    <string name="youtube_3">IfKNOUUtyCA</string>
    <string name="youtube_4">7n1P7a20hF8</string>
    <string name="youtube_5">92m5VXkjBTo</string>
    <string name="youtube_6">q0TOs5kYXhI</string>
    <string name="youtube_7">Ah7lTT-NKMw</string>
    <string name="youtube_8">2docezZl574</string>
    <string name="youtube_9">WeuqTw0EiZw</string>
    <string name="youtube_10">pgjcbIi2x38</string>


</resources>